Adrian Dobrzycki

About me

SOLID-ly oriented on design pattern backend .NET developer with over 15 years of experience. Specialized in building and understanding complex enterprise-level solutions. Open source contributor, libraries & frameworks builder. Uses SQL to set up new relations. Loving testing and 'it depends' design pattern.

TL;DR

How to describe me as a programmer in a few words?

- it depends
- · understand and rebuild
- understand and invent
- make it work
- make it truly work
- don't like javascript

Contact

- adrian.dobrzycki@gmail.com
- born in '86
- · Warsaw, Poland

Core skills

Back-end

- C#, .net: Core2+, 5.0, 4.6+, WCF
- CQRS, DI, SQL, SOLID, QUEUE-es, RxNet
- SQL, T-SQL, MsSQL, MySQL, Oracle, PL/SQL basics, EntityFramework, MongoDB, LINQ
- REST, SOAP, JSON/BSON
- JWT, OAuth
- xUnit, NUnit, Moq, NSubstitute
- Azure basics

Front-end

- Winforms, DevExpress
- basics: Blazor, Typescript, Javascript (ES6+), Angular 4+, jQuery, HTML, CSS

General

- SCRUM, R#
- Windows, GIT, PowerShell, Windows CE
- Jenkins, Jira, TeamCity, Octopus Deploy

• IIS, Kestrel, TCP/IP

Work history

06.2018 - 09.2020 - Senior .NET Developer (core team member) - PGE Systemy S.A.

Building a complex enterprise-level application based on .NET core 3+ and Angular 4+ using SCRUM methodology. Member of 'core team' produces standards and designing architecture.

- taking care of system architecture
- design and implementing shared features (privileges, locking, queues, transactions)
- code refactoring
- .NET mentoring

.NET Core 3+, C#, GIT, Jira, Jenkins, Angular 8+, TypeScript, CQRS, IoC/DI (Autofac), xUnit, LINQ, Moq, Rx.NET, RxJs, PL/SQL, RabbitMq, R#, DataGrip, Oracle

01.2014 - 04.2018 - Team Leader - PPH POLCAR

Working on architecture and application development standards for high performant and HA (high availability) application. Managing team.

- design and implement system architecture
- tasks sharing, team mentoring
- implementing product

NET 4.6+, C#, GIT, VSTS, CQRS, IoC/DI (Autofac), xUnit, LINQ, NLog, NSubstitute, Rx.NET, TeamCity, Octopus Deploy, lz4Net, WinForms + DevExpress, JSON/BSON, SOAP, WCF, .NET Core 2.0+, TCP/IP, T-SQL, MySql, EF6, IIS, Resharper, AutoMapper, VS2017, nuget

01.2012 - 01.2014 - Senior .NET Developer - PPH POLCAR

Building new and maintaining existing systems for internal company usage.

- design and implement system architecture for new projects
- · refactoring of existing projects and architectures
- maintaining existing products

T-SQL, WinForms + DevExpress, NET4.0+, NETCF3.5+, Resco, VS2008 + VS2012+, Resharper, TFS, IIS, WCF, WPF, ASPX, IIS, XPO, JavaScript

09.2008 - 01.2012 - .NET Developer - PPH POLCAR

Building WMS and CRM systems for internal company usage. Maintaining existing solutions.

- implementing new features for existing solutions
- maintaining products
- design and implement system architecture for mobile applications (Windows CE)

T-SQL, WinForms + DevExpress, NET2.0/4.0, NETCF 2.0/3.5, Resco, VS2008/2010/2012, SVN, TFS, IIS, ASMX, ASPX, JavaScript, XPO, Resharper, IIS, Windows CE

Education

• 09.2005 - 09.2009 - Białystok University of Technology (Bachelor of Engineering)

Languages

- English (B1-speaking, B2+ understanding)
- Polish (native)

Hobbies

Programming, good book/movie, bicycle, chess. Participation in meetups and technical conferences.

Some of my projects

- https://github.com/adobrzyc/modulos
- https://github.com/adobrzyc/modulos.messaging
- https://github.com/adobrzyc/modulos.testing
- https://github.com/adobrzyc/modulos.testing.db

More at

- github: https://github.com/adobrzyc
- linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/adrian-dobrzycki-a26833134
- stackoverflow: https://stackoverflow.com/users/5320247/adobrzyc

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my application to be processed by anyone for the purpose of current and future recruitment processes under the Personal Data Protection Act. I provide my personal data voluntarily understanding that without it a proper recruitment process is deemed impossible.